让我们开始为我们的数据和我们的模型之间定义一个协议。
Let's start by defining a database contract between our data and
这个协议是建立在我们的数据模型和
our model. A contract is an agreement between our data model and
我们描述信息是怎么储存的观点之间的。它包含了所有将要显示在我们用户界面
views describing how information is stored. It will contain all the fields that
的所有字段。那就让我们开始在Android Studio上编写代码吧。
our user interface will display. Let's go into Android Studio to begin coding.
我们要在我们的工程中添加一个新的程序包，我们给他命为data，然后把数据模型放到这里边。
We'll add a new package to our project named data to encapsulate the data model.
接下来，我们要新建一个合约类，让他储存我们的列信息。
Next, we'll create a contract class to store our column information.
在我们合约类里的内部类将被用作定义表格。
The inner classes within our contract class will be used to define tables.
每一个表格都将实现base columns因为通过base columns表述的列是很有用的。
Each table will implement base columns because the columns represented by base
特别是这个ID列，必须是我们表格的一部分，
columns are useful. The ID column, in particular, must be part of our table
也是为了以后我们的内容提供者集成工作。
in order for our content provider integration to work later on in this lesson